A Finding Aid to the National Arts Club Records, 1898-1960, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Administration, 1898-1960, undated; Series 2; Archival Resource Key
  - Officers' Correspondence, 1898-1960, undated; 2.1; Archival Resource Key
    The Officers' Correspondence subseries includes several categories: General correspondence (organized chronologically), and subject files on mortgage bonds, exhibitions, studio building, and insurance. Officers represented are mainly the Secretary, Assistant Secretary, and President, but there is also correspondence of others including the Board of Governors, chairmen of various committees, and the Treasurer.
    Records relating to exhibitions typically include correspondence, sales, consignment and other accounting records, shipping receipts, catalog dummies and galley proofs, and miscellaneous publicity material.
    An addition of Officers' Correspondence with artists about the club was added to the collection in 2017. This material is dated circa 1898 to 1934.
    - Correspondence, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4240, Frame 976-1020)
    - Correspondence, circa 1898-1934; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1898; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4240, Frame 1021-1062)
      (opinions of Charles L. Freer, Charles Henry Hart, Augustus Saint-Gaudens, Alfred Stieglitz, Stanford White, and others, offered in response to a circular describing the proposed National Arts Club)
    - Correspondence, 1898, cont.; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 6-58)
    - Correspondence, 1898; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1899; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241)
      William T. Evans on the inception of his collection
    - Correspondence, 1899; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1900 [Oct.-Dec. precedes Apr.-Sept.]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 131-263)
      (Charles Volkmar on decorative arts and gift of vases to NAC, report of Frederick Law Olmsted on site chosen for the Tome Institute, Port Deposit, Md., printed circular of NAC on decoration of the National Capitol with text of a bill to create a Capitol Art Commission, and Louis Agassiz Fuertes's letter about his exhibition with a list of pieces to be shown)
    - Correspondence, 1900; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1901; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 264-333)
      (Pan American Pacific Exposition instructions for exhibitors)
    - Correspondence, 1901; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1902; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 334-350)
    - Correspondence, 1902; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1903; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 351-364)
      (John Q. A. Ward on changes in management of NAC, and Bancel La Farge on proper lighting for exhibition of stained glass windows)
    - Correspondence, 1903; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1904; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 365-404)
      (American Institute of Architects protest against proposed Dept. of Agriculture buildings that would interfere with L'Enfant plan for D.C., with map)
    - Correspondence, 1904; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1905; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 405-430)
    - Correspondence, 1905; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1906; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 431-440)
    - Correspondence, 1906; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1907; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 441-460)
    - Correspondence, 1907; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1908; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 461-479)
    - Correspondence, 1908; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1909; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 480-524)
      (John de Witt Warner on the role of women in the National Arts Club)
    - Correspondence, 1909; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1910; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 525-553)
      (lists of important papers in the custody of the Club Secretary)
    - Correspondence, 1911; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 554-556)
    - Correspondence, 1912; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 557-560)
    - Correspondence, 1912; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1913; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 561-582)
      (petition requesting life membership to honor Frederick S. Lamb)
    - Correspondence, 1913; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1914; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 583-586)
    - Correspondence, 1915; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 587-597)
      (correspondence concerning competition for best critical manuscript on the Altman Collection)
    - Correspondence, 1916; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 598-606)
    - Correspondence, 1917; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 607-615)
    - Correspondence, 1918; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 616-909)
      (petition and correspondence concerning controversy involving Club Treasurer Alexander Konta, with transcript of "Cross Examination of Mr. Alexander Konta on Brewing and Liquor Interest and German Propaganda, Hearings before a Sub-Committee on the Judiciary, U.S. Senate)
    - Correspondence, 1919; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 910-983)
      (brochure about Co-Operative Art Building)
    - Correspondence, 1920; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 984-1013)
    - Correspondence, 1921; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 1014-1018)
    - Correspondence, 1921; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1922; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 1019-1022)
    - Correspondence, 1922; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1924; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 1023-1068)
      (form letter from John Quinn requesting NAC support in his fight to remove tax on art sales)
    - Correspondence, 1924; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1925; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 1069-1075)
    - Correspondence, 1926; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1927; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 1076-1106)
      (additional documents concerning Alexander Konta, and legal papers regarding objection of NAC to zoning changes proposed for neighboring property)
    - Correspondence, 1927; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1928; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1929; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4241, Frame 1107-1120)
    - Correspondence, 1930-1931; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4242, Frame 6-1072)
      ("Soul of America" contest sponsored by NAC)
    - Correspondence, 1931; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1933; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4242, Frame 1073)
    - Correspondence, 1933; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1934; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4242, Frame 1074)
    - Correspondence, 1934; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1935; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4242, Frame 1075-1163)
      (reminiscences of NAC's early years solicited from long-time members, including replies from J. William Fosdick, Dr. William Bainbridge, Thomas G. Taaffe, George P. Peabody, and Charles Vezin)
    - Correspondence, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4242, Frame 1164-1166)
    - Correspondence, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4242, Frame 1167-1228)
      (George Chapellier's notes on restoration of paintings exhibited at NAC)
    - Correspondence, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4242, Frame 1229-1395)
      (suggestion of J. Frederick Talcott to sell works by artist life members in order to raise money)
    - Correspondence, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4242, Frame 1396-1434)
      (correspondence with Helen Hayes concerning election to life membership)
    - Correspondence, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4243, Frame 6-323)
    - Correspondence, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4243, Frame 324-337)
    - Correspondence, 1943; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4243, Frame 338-359)
    - Correspondence, 1944; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4243, Frame 360-369)
    - Correspondence, 1945; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4243, Frame 369-373)
    - Correspondence, 1947; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4243, Frame 374)
    - Correspondence, 1948; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4243, Frame 375)
    - Correspondence, 1953; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4243, Frame 376-385)
    - Correspondence, 1954; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4243, Frame 386-408)
      (proposed amendments to constitution, and extensive suggestions of Walter Zahn for improved administration)
    - Correspondence, 1956; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4243, Frame 409-412)
    - Correspondence, 1957; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4243, Frame 413-438)
      (revision of constitution)
    - Correspondence, 1958; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4243, Frame 439-440)
    - Correspondence, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4243, Frame 441-455)
    - Correspondence, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4243, Frame 456-464)
      (amendments to Certificate of Incorporation, and establishment of Gregg Memorial Room)
  - War Tax Refund (see also Series 2: Administration, Treasurer), Archival Resource Key (Reel 4243)
    - Application and Supporting Documentation, 1922; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4243, Frame 467-816)
    - Correspondence with Treasury Department, Internal Revenue, and Attorneys, 1919-1922; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4243, Frame 817-941)
    - Correspondence with Organizations Requesting Information, 1922-1924; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4243, Frame 942-963)
    - Sample Form Letters to Members, 1922; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4243, Frame 964-967)
    - Correspondence with Members, 1922-1923; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4243, Frame 968-1384)
    - Correspondence with Members, 1922-1923, cont.; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4244, Frame 6-266)
  - Mortgage Bonds (see also Series 1: Board of Governors, Special Committee of Second Mortgage Gondholder), Archival Resource Key (Reel 4244)
    - Memorandum summarizing background of First and Second Mortgage Bonds, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4244, Frame 268-276)
  - Arts Realty Co., Archival Resource Key (Reel 4244)
    - First Mortgage Bond - Subscriber Lists, 1906-1907, 1918; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4244, Frame 277-281)
    - First Mortgage Bond - Correspondence, 1918-1919, 1927-1928; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4244, Frame 282-789)
    - First Mortgage Bondholders' Coupons Paid (1 volume - only sample page microfilmed), 1919-1928; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4244, Frame 790-792)
    - Second Mortgage Bond - Subscriber Lists, 1906-1929, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4244, Frame 793-856)
    - Participation Trust Agreement concerning Second Mortgage Bond, 1918; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4244, Frame 857-886)
    - Second Mortgage Bond Certificate photostats, 1918; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4244, Frame 887-890)
    - Transfers, Assignments, and Miscellaneous Legal Documents concerning Second Mortgage Bond, 1911-1922, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4244, Frame 891-960)
    - Second Mortgage Bond - Correspondence, 1910-1930; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4244, Frame 961-1281)
    - Second Mortgage Bondholders' Coupons Paid (only sample page microfilmed), 1907-1926; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4244, Frame 1282-1284)
  - Exhibitions, Archival Resource Key (Reel 4244)
    - Decorative Arts Exhibition, 1928; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4244, Frame 1287-1340)
    - Decorative Arts Exhibition, 1928, cont.; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4245, Frame 5-558)
    - Books of the Year Exhibition, 1928; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4245, Frame 561-1053)
    - Decorative Arts Exhibition, 1929; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4245, Frame 1054-1361)
      (correspondence, sales and consignment records)
    - Decorative Arts Exhibition, 1929; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4245, Frame 4-636)
      (shipping receipts, mailing lists, publicity, and a book of entry blanks and receipts)
    - Decorative Arts Exhibition, 1929, cont.; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4246, Frame 4-636)
    - Sixth Annual Exhibition of Living American Etchers, 1929; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4246, Frame 638-1186)
    - Decorative Arts Exhibition, 1930; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4246, Frame 1187-1205)
    - Twenty-Fifth Anniversary Exhibition of Books of the Year, 1930; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4246, Frame 1206-1214)
      (list of participating publishers)
    - Seventh Annual Exhibition of Living American Etchers (target incorrectly reads Decorative Arts Exhibition), 1930; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4246, Frame 1215-1378)
    - Seventh Annual Exhibition of Living American Etchers, 1930, cont.; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4247, Frame 4-152)
    - Books of the Year Exhibition, 1946; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4247, Frame 153-918)
    - Books of the Year Exhibition, 1947; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4247, Frame 919-1393)
    - Books of the Year Exhibition, 1947, cont.; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4248, Frame 4-443)
    - Books of the Year Exhibition, 1948; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4248, Frame 444-1374)
    - Books of the Year Exhibition, 1948, cont.; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4249, Frame 4-178)
    - Books of the Year Exhibition, 1949; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4249, Frame 179-1169)
    - Books of the Year Exhibition, 1950; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4249, Frame 1170-1315)
    - Books of the Year Exhibition, 1950, cont.; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4250, Frame 6-146)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary Exhibition of Books of the Year, 1956; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4250, Frame 148-214)
    - Books of the Year Exhibition, 1957; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4250, Frame 215-217)
    - International Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture (target omitted), 1957; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4250, Frame 218-312)
  - Studio Building, Archival Resource Key (Reel 4250)
    - Lists of Applicants, Tenants, etc., Archival Resource Key (Reel 4250, Frame 317-342)
    - Correspondence, A-Z, 1920-1932; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4250, Frame 343-1073)
    - Leases and Related Legal Papers, 1923-1929; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4250, Frame 1074-1124)
  - Insurance, Archival Resource Key (Reel 4250)
    - Appraisal and Inventory including art collection, 1920, 1954; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4250, Frame 1129-1169)
    - Policies and Related Correspondence (for building and contents, including fine arts), Archival Resource Key (Reel Unfilmed)
    - Unidentified Policies, and Correspondence Regarding More than One Category of Insurance, Archival Resource Key (Reel Unfilmed)
  - President, 1920, 1928; 2.2; Archival Resource Key
    Correspondence found here concerns general Club business and the activities of various standing committees. Also included is printed matter issued by NAC and other arts organizations.
    - Correspondence, Jan.-May 1920, 1928; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4250, Frame 1172-1372)
    - Jan.-May 1920, 1928, cont., Archival Resource Key (Reel 4251, Frame 4-314)
  - Secretary, 1927-1939; 2.3; Archival Resource Key
    Correspondence in this subseries concerns resignations.
    - Correspondence, A-Z, 1927-1932; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4251, Frame 318-1401)
    - Correspondence, A-Z, 1927-1932, cont.; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4252, Frame 4-24)
    - Correspondence, A-Z, 1933-1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4252, Frame 25-1445)
    - Correspondence, A-Z, 1933-1939, cont.; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4253, Frame 4-42)
  - President, 1917-1957, undated; 2.4; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries begins with Tresurer's notebooks which contain correspondence, reports, and annotated copies of Board of Executive Committee minutes. Working papers include comparative statistics, balance sheets and printed Treasurer's reports, in addition to correspondence.
    For additional information relating to the records in this subseries see Series 2.1: Officers' Correspondence, War Tax Refund and Mortgage Bonds; Series 3: Financial Records; and Series 8.1, Treasurer's Reports.
    - Treasurer's Notebook Volume 1, 1917-1919; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4253, Frame 48-163)
    - Treasurer's Notebook Volume 2, 1919-1922; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4253, Frame 164-311)
    - Treasurer's Notebook Volume 3, 1922-1926; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4253, Frame 312-461)
    - Treasurer's Notebook Volume 4, 1926-1931; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4253, Frame 462-552)
    - Treasurer's Notebook Volume 5, 1931-1934; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4253, Frame 553-632)
    - Treasurer's Notebook Volume 6, 1934-1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4253, Frame 633-703)
    - Treasurer's Notebook Volume 7, 1938-1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4253, Frame 704-776)
    - Working Papers, 1918-1931; Archival Resource Key; (1 volume) (Reel 4253, Frame 777-921)
    - Working Papers, 1918-1931, cont.; Archival Resource Key; (1 volume) (Reel 4254, Frame 11-29)
    - Purchase of Internal Revenue Stamps (Act of Oct. 22, 1914), 1917; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4254, Frame 30-77)
    - Correspondence re: Taxes, 1932, 1938-1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4254, Frame 78-117)
    - General Correspondence, A-Z, 1943-1957; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4254, Frame 118-366)
    - Miscellaneous, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4254, Frame 367-371)
  - Manager, 1956-1960; 2.5; Archival Resource Key
    This series concerns arrangements for events held at the Club (both NAC and non-NAC sponsored), restaurant, accommodations for members visiting from out of town, and use of gallery space with detailed schedules for 1957-1958.
    - Correspondence (filmed twice), 1956-1960; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4254, Frame 374-1161)
  - House Committee, 1922-1932; 2.6; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries contains correspondence about house rules, condition of the building, and the needs and problems of residents and those renting studios.
    - Correspondence, A-Z, 1922-1932; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4254, Frame 1165-1445)
    - Correspondence, A-Z, 1922-1932, cont.; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4255, Frame 4-384)
  - American Artists' War Emergency Fund Committee, 1917-1918; 2.7; Archival Resource Key
    The correspondence found here mainly concerns issuing stamps to raise money for financial aid to art workers suffering financial reverses due to the war and to help increase food production for the country at large. Included are sample stamps designed by Eugene Savage, and printed matter of the American Artists' War Emergency Fund Committee.
    - Correspondence, 1917-1918; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4255, Frame 387-481)
  - Men's Open Table, 1915-1950; 2.8; Archival Resource Key
    Correspondence found in this subseries concerns the selection of speakers, comments by members about programs, some announcements of meetings, and printed matter about speakers. The noices of Men's Open Table meetings comprise one announcement per page, accompanied by signatures of members in attendance; also included are Ipson sketches of speakers: Dr. Elwood Hendrick, April 26, 1928; Prof. J.W. Jenks, Feb. 14, 1927; Col. Norman Schwartzkopf, Dec. 5, 1927; Gregory Zilboorg, March 12, 1928; and of members Billy [Hutchinson], Dec. 5, 1927, and Mason Chase, Jan. 16, 1928. There is also the poem, "To the Mens Open Table," by Frank Chapin Bray, Nov. 1926.
    For related information see also Series 8.1: National Arts Club Printed Matter and Series 9: Scrapbooks.
    - Correspondence, A-Z, 1915-1916, 1918; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4255, Frame 485-700)
    - Correspondence, A-Z, 1922-1929; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4255, Frame 701-1215)
    - Correspondence, A-Z, 1922-1929, cont.; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4256, Frame 4-550)
    - Miscellaneous, Archival Resource Key (Reel 4256, Frame 551-587)
    - Dinner in honor of William S. Hutchinson, 1928; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4256, Frame 588-618)
    - "Memories of the Men's Open Table of the National Arts Club," by John R. Gregg, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4256, Frame 619-651)
    - Notices of Men's Open Table meetings, Volume 1, 1919-1925; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4256, Frame 652-766)
    - Notices of Men's Open Table meetings, Volume 2, 1925-1929; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4256, Frame 767-981)
    - Notices of Men's Open Table meetings, Volume 2, 1942-1950; Archival Resource Key (Reel 4256, Frame 892-934)
- Financial Records, 1917-1952; Series 3; Archival Resource Key
  This series contains general ledgers and cashbooks, accounts of special funds, and Treasurer's reports. Correspondence of the Treasurer and other officers is especially thorough regarding application for and use of a refund of war tax levied on membership dues in 1917/18, and concerning First and Second Mortgage Bonds issued to finance the clubhouse. For additional information relating to these records see Series 2.1: Officers Correspondence, War Tax Refund and Mortgage Bonds; and Series 8.1: National Arts Club Printed Matter, Treasurer's Reports.
  - Special Fund, December 1917; Archival Resource Key; (1 volume) (Reel unfilmed)
  - Ledgers, 1922-1927, 1939-1949; Archival Resource Key; (2 volumes) (Reel unfilmed)
  - Treasurer's Monthly Statements, 1923-1929; Archival Resource Key; (1 volume) (Reel unfilmed)
  - General Cash Books, 1939-1946, 1946-1952; Archival Resource Key; (2 volumes) (Reel unfilmed)
  - Cash Receipts, 1947-1949; Archival Resource Key; (1 volume) (Reel unfilmed)
  - Account Book, 1949-1950; Archival Resource Key; (disbound volume) (Reel unfilmed)
- Membership, circa 1900-1962; Series 4; Archival Resource Key
  Records consist of membership rolls from 1940 to 1952 (11 volumes), and rosters from 1931 to 1959. Membership rosters contain alphabetical listings by name, including address, telephone number, category of membership, and date of election, with notes on date and reason for discontinuation of membership. For additional information relating to these records see Series 2.3: Secretary and Series 8.1: National Arts Council Printed Matter, Membership Lists.
  Membership rolls are arranged by membership category; rosters are arranged alphabetically
  - Membership Rolls, Archival Resource Key (Reel unfilmed)
    - Volume 1: Resident, Junior Lay, Younger Artists, Suburban, May 1940-May 1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel unfilmed)
    - Volume 2: Resident, Junior Lay, Younger Artists, Suburban, May 1942-May 1944; Archival Resource Key (Reel unfilmed)
    - Volume 3: Non-Resident Priviledged, Non-Resident, Associate, May 1942-May 1944; Archival Resource Key (Reel unfilmed)
    - Volume 4: Non-Resident Priviledged, Non-Resident, Associate, May 1944-May 1946; Archival Resource Key (Reel unfilmed)
    - Volume 5: Resident, Junior Lay, Younger Artists, Suburban, May 1944-May 1946; Archival Resource Key (Reel unfilmed)
    - Volume 6: Non-Resident Priviledged, Non-Resident, Associate, May 1946-May 1948; Archival Resource Key (Reel unfilmed)
    - Volume 7: Resident, Junior Lay, Younger Artists, Suburban, May 1946-May 1948; Archival Resource Key (Reel unfilmed)
    - Volume 8: Resident, Junior Lay, Younger Artists, Suburban, May 1948-May 1950; Archival Resource Key (Reel unfilmed)
    - Volume 9: Non-Resident Priviledged, Non-Resident, Associate, May 1948-May 1950; Archival Resource Key (Reel unfilmed)
    - Volume 10: Non-Resident Priviledged, Non-Resident, May 1950-May 1952; Archival Resource Key (Reel unfilmed)
    - Volume 11: Resident, Junior Lay, Junior Artists, Suburban, Associate, May 1950-May 1952; Archival Resource Key (Reel unfilmed)
  - Membership Rosters, Archival Resource Key (Reel 4256)